<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Development in Chicago</title>
    <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Software Development in Chicago</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:14:19 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing to people should be continuous</title>
      <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/2019-01-14_marketing_to_people_should_be_continious/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:14:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/2019-01-14_marketing_to_people_should_be_continious/</guid>
      <description> Marketing to people should be continuous  old fashion marketing required you to put ads on tv and papers there should be a better way, more continous way advertising lets you have your ads permanently present yes social media efforts require a lot of effort to do things right solution for marketing on social media at scale  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Ready For 2019</title>
      <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/2018-12-31_getting_ready_for_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:14:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/2018-12-31_getting_ready_for_2019/</guid>
      <description>New year is coming tomorrow. A lot of great things are ahead of me.
Independence streak This all started sometime 2017, in March, then this whole year was awesome, I worked in Elm, developed two products. Had great summer, observed Eclipse.
Joining big org Then near the end, I joined Allstate. This got me into really cool and interesting organization. Sometime in November this year, I joined Arity, which is Allstate company focused on using data to enhance our mobility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devengine Stalled</title>
      <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/devengine_stalled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 15:17:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/devengine_stalled/</guid>
      <description>My adventure with devEngine started really well, but after a while all activity just stupped, which really is sad, as this is great project. I tried several things to review it and but nothing seemed to work.
From this perspective, it is obvious some of the issues I had, but nothing was really huge, for some reason we didn&amp;rsquo;t gain traction.
For now it is stopped but I am working on some way to get it up and running again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topics for writing</title>
      <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 15:17:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/topics/</guid>
      <description> Design is watefall, development is iterative Marketing to people should be continuous How to be succesful online why people will not work in your startup/corporation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netlify Impresses</title>
      <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/netlify_impresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 03:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/netlify_impresses/</guid>
      <description>So, this site lay fallow for a little bit, like a year or so :). Maybe less. I was really busy. Seriously.
So now I had some time and read through few articles about how people deploy their sites. I knew about Netlify from before, but made me look again and it is really super awesome and simple to have site with them. Static sites are their thing and it is a joy to see, just update site, commit to git and things happen in the background and boom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to new site, welcome to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 01:02:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softwaredevelopmentinchicago.com/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>This is my new site. I went through a lot of false starts. Tried a lot of different tools to publish my thoughts, you would think I write a lot since I was obesessing so much about how to make it as easy as possible.
Winner In the end, here we are, Hugo is the winner.
It started with Middleman I started originally with Middleman. I got frustrated as theming took too much time and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t super focused to begin with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>